Search 

Select your language

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

* * *

    * Break

* Get Help

Search 

Select your language

* Break

Privacy Policy
==============

We are committed to protecting your privacy and keeping you informed of how your personal information is used. This Privacy Policy applies to personal data we collect through the proxmox.com website, and other websites which we operate and on which we post a link to this policy. We will only collect and use your personal information in accordance with the current EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the Austrian data protection law Datenschutzgesetz (DSG), and the Telekommunikationsgesetz (TKG).

Have questions concerning collected data and privacy? Please contact us:

Proxmox Server Solutions GmbH  
Bräuhausgasse 37  
1050 Vienna, Austria  

Date: May 24, 2018

### Personal Data

By using the Proxmox website and its subdomains (such as forum.proxmox.com, pve.proxmox.com/wiki, my.proxmox.com, etc.) you consent to the collection, retention and use of your personal information in accordance with the terms of this policy. We only collect personal information from you if you interact with us through our websites when you for example fill out a contact form, email us, create a user account, purchase/register a product or service, request support, or apply for a job.

We use this information provided by you only for our own business purposes (for dispatching the requested material/information), and will never disclose it to third parties, whether for commercial or non-commercial purposes. Furthermore, we protect your personal information with appropriate safeguards. You may withdraw your consent at any time to take effect for future use.

### Use of data when registering for the email newsletter

If you are a registered user of a Proxmox newsletter and have supplied your email address, Proxmox may occasionally email you to tell you about new features, new services, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Proxmox and our products. We do anonymize your interaction with our newsletter. If you subsequently wish to opt out, you can do so by clicking the unsubscribe link in our newsletter emails, or you can contact us at the address above. This information will not be disclosed to third parties.

### Your Rights

According to the EU GDPR and to the DSG you have the right to access, rectify, and to erase your personal data, the right to ask for a copy of the information held by us in our records or to restrict our use of your personal data. Please contact us at the address above.

### Log Data

Generally, you may use our website without disclosing your identity and personal data. What we collect is the information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website (log data). The data collected includes for example:

* Referrer (page from which our website was accessed)
* Search terms (if a search engine was the referrer)
* IP is anonymous but evaluated to determine the country of origin and the provider
* Browser, operating system, installed plug-ins and screen resolution
* Time spent on the website

### Public Forum Reminder

Proxmox subdomains include a forum, a wiki, a customer portal, and mailing lists which are available to users. These are public areas, so please remember that any information that is disclosed there becomes public. Think twice before disclosing your personal data or your company data there if you don't want them to become public.

### Matomo

This website and our subdomains use Matomo (formerly known as Piwik), an open-source web analytics software. It is used to monitor the use of our website to help us improve our information and services. We do anonymize your IP address and all data will be stored on our own servers in the European Union.

### Cookies

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser and stored on your device. Most of the cookies we use are session cookies and will be deleted after the end of your browser session; some are persistent for a certain amount of time and allow recognizing your browser within the next session (for example, if you choose the “remember me” sign in preference).

You can change your browser settings to restrict or block some or all cookies. Check the information provided in your browser’s help section for specific instructions on how to manage cookies. Opting out or blocking some cookies may affect the functionality of the website (such as to remember preferences).

### Consent

You can withdraw your previously given consent in the cookie settings or give consent in order to regain full functionality of the site.

### Products

### Resources

### Newsletter

Email \*

I agree with the privacy policy \*

Subscribe  

Copyright © 2004 - 2024 Proxmox Server Solutions GmbH. All rights reserved.
